Here's our imaginary project that's got the different branches.
Este é nosso projeto imaginário com diferentes branches.
Let's say we want to merge the master and sidebar branches together.
Vamos fazer o merge dos branches master e sidebar.
When a merge happens, it makes a commit.
Quando o merge ocorre, isso cria um commit.
Since head is pointing to the master branch,
Como HEAD está apontando para o branch master,
the merge commit will be placed on the master branch and it will move forward.
o commit merge será posicionado nele e ele seguirá adiante.
Let's merge sidebar into master.
Vamos fazer o merge do sidebar com o master.
Notice that a merge commit links to two different earlier commits.
Perceba que o commit merge se liga aos dois commits anteriores.
This doesn't affect the sidebar branch.
Isto não afetará o branch sidebar.
We can switch back to it and still make commits on it.
Ainda podemos mudar para ele e criar commits.
Let's say we had a social links branch that's a bit ahead of the master branch.
Imagine um branch social-links, que está à frente do master.
The master branch doesn't have the social links commits in it yet.
O branch master não tem commits do social-links ainda.
If we want those commits in the master branch we would
Se quisermos esses commits no branch master,
merge the social links branch into the master branch.
devemos fazer o merge do branch social-link no master.
Since head is pointing to master,
Como HEAD está apontando para master,
the master branch will move when a merge is made.
o branch master se moverá quando o merge for feito.
Now because the social links branch is just ahead of master,
Como o branch social-link está à frente do master,
GIT we'll do what's called a fast forward merge.
Git fará um merge fast forward.
Also, the order of the colored lines doesn't matter here.
A ordem das linhas coloridas não importa aqui,
We can move the red line to the top and nothing changes.
podemos mover a linha vermelha para cima e nada mudará.
The lines are just there to connect commits together.
As linhas só servem para unir commits.